Question_data = [
    {"question": "Lists in Python are mutable.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Dictionary keys can be duplicated.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "You can access list elements using indexing.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Dictionaries are ordered in Python 3.7 and above.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "You can use a list as a dictionary key.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "The append() method adds an element at the end of a list.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The keys() method returns all dictionary values.", "answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Lists can contain different data types in the same list.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "pop() works for both lists and dictionaries.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Dictionaries use indexing like dict[0] to access the first element.", "answer": "False"}
]

